module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the most expensive spice in the world?',
      a: 'Cardamom',
      b: 'Cinnamon',
      c: 'Vanilla',
      d: 'Saffron',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which pepper ranks the highest on the Scoville Heat Scale at a whopping 2.2 million SHU?',
      a: 'Trinidad Scorpion Butch T',
      b: 'Carolina Reaper',
      c: 'Infinity Chili',
      d: 'Ghost Pepper',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which spice gives pizza its characteristic flavor?',
      a: 'Oregano',
      b: 'Basil',
      c: 'Garlic',
      d: 'Parmesan Cheese',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Not all oils are created equally. Which has the highest smoke point and is best for deep frying?',
      a: 'Avocado Oil',
      b: 'Peanut Oil',
      c: 'Olive Oil',
      d: 'Hemp Seed Oil',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the most widely used culinary herb in the United States?',
      a: 'Cilantro',
      b: 'Parsley',
      c: 'Rosemary',
      d: 'Thyme',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Peppercorns come in a few varieties: black, white, green, red, pink. Which peppercorn statement is false?',
      a: 'White come from black',
      b: 'Black come from green',
      c: 'Red come from green',
      d: 'Pink come from red',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these Indian style dishes is going to leave you most wanting a glass of milk?',
      a: 'Vindaloo',
      b: 'Tikka Masala',
      c: 'Red Curry',
      d: 'Green Curry',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which salt packs the most punch on the rim of a margarita?',
      a: 'Kosher Salt',
      b: 'Sea Salt',
      c: 'Fleur de Sel',
      d: 'Himalayan Pink Salt',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Lavender has had many uses historically. Which of the following has lavender NOT been used for?',
      a: 'Bug Repellent',
      b: 'Reduce Fevers',
      c: 'Mummification',
      d: 'Furniture Polish',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many poppyseeds would you need to ingest today in order to test positive on a drug test for opiates?',
      a: 'One poppyseed bagel',
      b: '3 tsp of poppyseeds',
      c: '5 tsp of poppyseeds',
      d: '1 cup of poppyseeds',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};